<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>hey.paris</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on hey.paris</description>
    <image>
      <title>hey.paris</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/images/cover.jpg</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/images/cover.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.129.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Dr Paris Buttfield-Addison</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Paris</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Dr Paris Buttfield-Addison is a creative technologist who works with everything from games and apps to narrative tools and educational resources.
He is co-founder and creative director of long-running Tasmanian game development studio Secret Lab, where he has worked on games for QANTAS, CSIRO, Marvel, the ABC, and more.
He is also co-founder of Yarn Spinner, a company spun out of the wildly successful game tool of the same name which is used in everything from university curricula to multiple IGF- and BAFTA-winning titles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/books-and-events/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/books-and-events/books/</guid>
      <description>Buttfield-Addison, P., Buttfield-Addison, M., Nugent, T., &amp;amp; Manning, J. (2022). Practical Simulations for Machine Learning. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media. Buttfield-Addison, P. &amp;amp; Manning, J. (2021). Head First Swift. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media. Buttfield-Addison, P., Manning, J., &amp;amp; Nugent, T. (2019). Unity Game Development Cookbook. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media. Out now! Geldard, M., Manning, J., Buttfield-Addison, P., &amp;amp; Nugent, T. (2019). Practical Artificial Intelligence with Swift. O&amp;rsquo;Reilly * Media. Manning, J., &amp;amp; Buttfield-Addison, P. (2018). iOS Swift Game Development Cookbook Third Edition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/books-and-events/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/books-and-events/events/</guid>
      <description>⚠️ I&amp;rsquo;m happy to speak at events on a range of topics, including game development and design, artifical intelligence, the intersection and implications of technology and creativity, space, technology, and beyond. Email me at paris AT paris.id.au to chat.
Upcoming Events 2024 Speaking: West Coast Space Show 2024, Tasmania, Australia Speaking: NZGDC 2024, Wellington, New Zealand Session: Let&amp;rsquo;s learn to write narrative games with Yarn Spinner Past Events 2024 Organising: AUC /dev/world/2024, Melbourne, Australia Organising: AUC XWorld 2024, Melbourne, Australia Speaking: NarraScope 2024, Rochester, NY, USA Workshop: Getting started with Yarn Spinner Speaking: North Bay Python 2024, Petaluma, CA, USA Session: Nighmare on LLM Street 2023 Speaking: Everything Open 2023, Melbourne, Australia Session: Let&amp;rsquo;s Use An Automated Theorem Prover To Verify Video Games Session: Don&amp;rsquo;t wait for Godot!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Coast Space Show</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/wcss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/wcss/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m absolutely thrilled to announce that, together with my wife Mars, I&amp;rsquo;ll be heading to the West and North West coasts of Tasmania to present a series of space-themed events and workshops for kids and adults alike.
We&amp;rsquo;ve called these events the West Coast Space Show. This National Science Week project is supported by the Australian Government.
This is an early step in our efforts to establish the West Coast Space Centre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now (also) buy Yarn Spinner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/yspl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/yspl/</guid>
      <description>Yarn Spinner is now available for purchase! We&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to make it easier for you to get started with Yarn Spinner, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce that you can now buy Yarn Spinner on the Unity Asset Store, and the Itch Store.
Yarn Spinner will always be free and open source, but we&amp;rsquo;re excited to offer a way for you to support the project and get some extra features and support in return.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
