<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Weekly Links on hey.paris</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/weekly-links/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Weekly Links on hey.paris</description>
    <image>
      <title>hey.paris</title>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/hobart.jpg</url>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/hobart.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.129.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Dr Paris Buttfield-Addison</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/weekly-links/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Links for August 29, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/weekly-links/08292024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/weekly-links/08292024/</guid>
      <description>Here are this week&amp;rsquo;s interesting links:
Dishwashers are critical: At the heart of every restaurant Hahahah, oh ho ho ho, hahahaha: Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Copilot falsely accuses court reporter of crimes he covered Astronomers back call for review of bonkers rule that means satellite swarms fly without environment checks Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Links for August 15 and August 22, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/weekly-links/08152024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/weekly-links/08152024/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the latest links. I was travelling the last two weeks, so I missed a week, and this one is late, but here we are:
The staggering death toll of scientific lies Finally, yes please: Artificial intelligence is losing hype From the &amp;lsquo;absolute crap&amp;rsquo; department: Peloton announces $95 “used equipment activation fee” Magic moment: Sydney aquarium filled with song after sea birds mourn death of gay penguin Sphen You don&amp;rsquo;t know how bad most things are nor precisely how they&amp;rsquo;re bad.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Links for August 8, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/weekly-links/08082024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/weekly-links/08082024/</guid>
      <description>And so it continues! Here&amp;rsquo;s my interesting links for this week:
Airlines Are Running Out Of Flight Numbers, And They Don’t Know What To Do About It New Euripides just dropped: Uncovered Euripides fragments are ‘kind of a big deal’ Should&amp;rsquo;ve just used that Brother printer everyone has: Reverse engineering the 59-pound printer onboard the Space Shuttle From the &amp;ldquo;they quoted my clever wife&amp;rdquo; department: Space is becoming an &amp;lsquo;unsustainable environment in the long term,&amp;rsquo; ESA says A public draft of the second edition of the brilliant Artificial Intelligence and Games book is available Computer Archeology: Exploring the Anatomy of an MS-DOS Virus (if you found this interesting you may also find this interesting) Last days of the lonely interstellar spacecraft (original here) See you next week!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Links for August 1, 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/weekly-links/08012024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/weekly-links/08012024/</guid>
      <description>With the death of Twitter, and the fracturing of social media, I&amp;rsquo;m going to try an experiment! To that end, I&amp;rsquo;m going post some of the more interesting things I&amp;rsquo;ve read online each Thursday. I hope you find them interesting too. Or not, I don&amp;rsquo;t mind. I&amp;rsquo;m just going to keep doing it anyway.
I&amp;rsquo;ll post links in no particular order, and they might not be recent. Just things I&amp;rsquo;ve found interesting in the previous week or so.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
